A Place in Time is a crime, drama film directed by Charles Lane.
A New York City street artist witnesses a crime and
resolves to redeem his earlier inaction.
A silent film in pantomime, this early work by director Charles Lane brings a
unique deftness and grace to its social realist narrative.
He would later revisit this theme in his next film Sidewalk Stories (1989).
The Artist, played by Charles Lane.
Orca (also known as Orca: The Killer Whale) is a 1977 thriller film directed by Michael Anderson, from a screenplay by Luciano Vincenzoni and Sergio Donati
based on a novel by Arthur Herzog, and starring Richard Harris, Charlotte Rampling, Will Sampson, Bo Derek, Keenan Wynn and Robert Carradine.
The film follows a male orca tracking down and getting revenge on a fishing boat and its
captain for unintentionally killing the whale's pregnant mate and their unborn calf.
Executive producer Dino De Laurentiis commissioned the project
to cash in on the blockbuster success of Jaws.
Filming took place in Newfoundland and Labrador and Malta, with many of the orca scenes
shot at the Marineland of the Pacific and the Marine World theme parks.
Upon release, the film was a minor box office success, but received mostly unfavorable reception from
critics and audiences alike due to its similarities to Jaws, released two years prior.
The film explores themes of new york city, witness,
street artist, black and white, silent film.
The tone is emotional.